<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<truthdare version="1.0">
  <truths>
    <truth id="t1">Who was your biggest crush that isnt your current partner?</truth>
    <truth id="t2">Do you remember the names of all the people you slept with?</truth>
    <truth id="t3">What is your biggest turn off?</truth>
    <truth id="t4">What is your biggest turn on?</truth>
    <truth id="t5">Has anyone ever threatened to break up with you?</truth>
    <truth id="t6">Who was your favorite ex?</truth>
    <truth id="t7">Are you left wing or right wing in politics?</truth>
    <truth id="t8">Who was the last candidate you voted for presidency?</truth>
    <truth id="t9">Did you ever creampied anyone/got creampied?</truth>
    <truth id="t10">What is your biggest guilty pleasure?</truth>
    <truth id="t11">What is your biggest fear/phobia?</truth>
    <truth id="t12">Have you ever faked orgasm?</truth>
    <truth id="t13">Have you ever cheated on someone?</truth>
    <truth id="t14">Did you ever had sex in public?</truth>
    <truth id="t15">Who was the last person you wanted to punch in the face?</truth>
    <truth id="t16">How many dating apps have you tried?</truth>
    <truth id="t17">Did you ever had a one night stand?</truth>
    <truth id="t18">Are you ever guilty of public display of affection?</truth>
    <truth id="t19">Do believe in higher power?</truth>
    <truth id="t20">Would you ever hookup with a transgender?</truth>
    <truth id="t21">What was the gayest thing you ever did?</truth>
    <truth id="t22">What sex toy you own if any?</truth>
    <truth id="t23">What is your biggest kink?</truth>
    <truth id="t24">Who would you fuck, marry, and kill?</truth>
    <truth id="t25">What is your favorite part of the body in terms of attractiveness?</truth>
    <truth id="t26">What would you name your autobiography?</truth>
    <truth id="t27">What is your favorite toy as a kid?</truth>
    <truth id="t28">What super power would you like to have?</truth>
    <truth id="t29">What language is the most attractive?</truth>
    <truth id="t30">What was the corniest/cringiest thing you ever done?</truth>
    <truth id="t31">What have you ever done that you regret the most?</truth>
    <truth id="t32">Did you ever got fired from a job?</truth>
    <truth id="t33">Have you ever made someone cry?</truth>
    <truth id="t34">Would you rather have a slutty daughter or a gay son?</truth>
    <truth id="t35">Would you rather have a daughter or a son?</truth>
    <truth id="t36">What was the last scene that made you cry?</truth>
    <truth id="t37">Who was the last person that made you cry?</truth>
    <truth id="t38">Who was the last person you had sex with that isn't your partner?</truth>
    <truth id="t39">Who was the last person that made you angry?</truth>
    <truth id="t40">If you could trade your life for someone who is currently dead, who would it be?</truth>
    <truth id="t41">How would you like to die one day?</truth>
    <truth id="t42">What do you like that you know everyone hates?</truth>
    <truth id="t43">What do you hate that you know everyone loves?</truth>
    <truth id="t44">When were you at the lowest point of your life?</truth>
    <truth id="t45">Have you ever sent nudes to someone?</truth>
    <truth id="t46">What was the last thing that made you depressed?</truth>
    <truth id="t47">If you could change one thing about yourself, what would it be?</truth>
    <truth id="t48">Who was the last person you personally know passed away?</truth>
    <truth id="t49">Do you remember the names of all the people you use to be friends with?</truth>
    <truth id="t50">Who is your biggest crush on a fictional character?</truth>
    <truth id="t51">What level is your sex drive on average?</truth>
    <truth id="t52">Have you ever been arrested?</truth>
    <truth id="t53">Who is the best kisser besides your partner?</truth>
    <truth id="t54">If you could be any animal, what would it be?</truth>
    <truth id="t55">If you could be any mythical creature, what would it be?</truth>
    <truth id="t56">Have you ever got someone killed or almost killed?</truth>
    <truth id="t57">Whats your least favorite ethnic group?</truth>
    <truth id="t58">Do you support Palestine or Israel?</truth>
    <truth id="t59">What would you name yourself if you become a serial killer?</truth>
    <truth id="t60">What did you/last person did to lose the friendship?</truth>
    <truth id="t61">What would you name yourself if you become a pornstar?</truth>
    <truth id="t62">What of the four elements would you like to be a bender of?</truth>
    <truth id="t63">Who would make the perfect main antagonist in your autobiography?</truth>
    <truth id="t64">Would you relive the last decade of your life with your memories intact?</truth>
    <truth id="t65">What was the scariest moment in your entire life?</truth>
    <truth id="t66">What physical aspect of yourself do you hate the most?</truth>
    <truth id="t67">What creature are you afraid of the most?</truth>
    <truth id="t68">What was the most offensive thing you've ever done?</truth>
    <truth id="t69">What is the most embarrassing thing that has happened to you?</truth>
    <truth id="t70">Have you ever attempted to or thought of take your own life?</truth>
    <truth id="t71">What was the last porn site you have visited?</truth>
    <truth id="t72">How hairy is your pubic hair?</truth>
    <truth id="t73">How hairy is your armpit hair?</truth>
    <truth id="t74">How hairy is your butt hair?</truth>
    <truth id="t75">What is your dick/bra size?</truth>
    <truth id="t76">Have you ever tried anal sex?</truth>
    <truth id="t77">Have you ever give/recieved a creampie?</truth>
    <truth id="t78">Who is the most annoying person you know?</truth>
    <truth id="t79">Have you ever paid for porn before?</truth>
    <truth id="t80">Have you ever took off a condom mid-sex?</truth>
    <truth id="t81">What was the worst crime you ever committed?</truth>
    <truth id="t82">When the last time you masturbate?</truth>
    <truth id="t83">Who is on the top of your flakers' list?</truth>
    <truth id="t84">Who is that one person you never invite to anything but still be friends?</truth>
    <truth id="t85">Who is the least attractive currently playing right now?</truth>
    <truth id="t86">Who is the most attractive currently playing right now?</truth>
    <truth id="t87">How often would you want to have sex?</truth>
    <truth id="t88">What do you think is your most attractive trait?</truth>
    <truth id="t89">Have you ever stood someone up in a date?</truth>
    <truth id="t90">Have you ever gotten stood up by someone?</truth>
    <truth id="t91">What was at one point you have the biggest main character syndrome?</truth>
    <truth id="t92">Who would you switch your life with someone that isn't your partner and currently playing?</truth>
    <truth id="t93">Do you prefer to be dominant or submissive in bed?</truth>
    <truth id="t94">Who would you fuck that isn't your partner and currently playing?</truth>
    <truth id="t95">Have you ever demanded to see the manager?</truth>
    <truth id="t96">If you could be any other ethnicity, what would it be?</truth>
    <truth id="t97">What was the weird thing you did during sex?</truth>
    <truth id="t98">What is the biggest deal breaker when it comes to relationships?</truth>
    <truth id="t99">What sex position you have done the most?</truth>
    <truth id="t100">What are the names of all the poeple you had sex with?</truth>
    <truth id="t101">Can you realistically take on everyone in this room in a brawl all at once?</truth>
    <truth id="t102">Can you realistically beat everyone in this room in a race?</truth>
    <truth id="t103">Have you ever been brainwashed before? Or aware enough to admit it?</truth>
    <truth id="t104">What kind of afterlife do you believe in?</truth>
    <truth id="t105">What family member you get along with the least?</truth>
    <truth id="t106">Have you ever had suicidal thoughts?</truth>
    <truth id="t107">If you could have homosexual intercourse with someone here, who would it be?</truth>
    <truth id="t108">If you could have sex with anyone here that isn't your partner, who would it be?</truth>
    <truth id="t109">Who here you think is the least attractive?</truth>
    <truth id="t110">Who here besides your partner, you think is the most attractive?</truth>
    <truth id="t111">If you were a serial killer, how would you kill people?</truth>
    <truth id="t112">What was your worst date?</truth>
    <truth id="t113">What was your most favorite date?</truth>
    <truth id="t114">How many people you were seeing the most all at once?</truth>
    <truth id="t115">Who did you gave your first kiss to?</truth>
    <truth id="t116">Who did you gave your virginity to?</truth>
    <truth id="t117">What was the most amount of dates you went on with but never became official?</truth>
    <truth id="t118">Have you ever went on social media to see how the people you stopped talking to are doing in life?</truth>
    <truth id="t119">If you could have a baby, what name would you give him/her?</truth>
    <truth id="t120">How many kids would you like have ideally?</truth>
  </truths>

  <dares>
    <dare id="d1">Dance to your favorite song</dare>
    <dare id="d2">Perform a sexy dance on someone who isn't your partner</dare>
    <dare id="d3">Dry hump someone who isn't your partner</dare>
    <dare id="d4">Give someone a lap dance who isn't your partner</dare>
    <dare id="d5">Give someone a hickey who isn't your partner</dare>
    <dare id="d6">Bite someone</dare>
    <dare id="d7">Do the Ukranian Hopak dance</dare>
    <dare id="d8">Perform 10 pushups</dare>
    <dare id="d9">Perform 10 jumping jacks</dare>
    <dare id="d10">Have someone ride you like a horse that isn't your partner</dare>
    <dare id="d11">Give someone the nastiest and sloppiest kiss possible</dare>
    <dare id="d12">Have someone smack your ass and say "harder daddy/mommy"</dare>
    <dare id="d13">Pretend to jerk someone off in the same sex while saying "Am I doing it right?"</dare>
    <dare id="d14">Re-enact your favorite sex position</dare>
    <dare id="d15">Rub ice on your bare feet and then eat it</dare>
    <dare id="d16">Swap your shirt with someone else</dare>
    <dare id="d17">Sing your favorite song as horribly as possible</dare>
    <dare id="d18">Prank call someone of your choosing for a pyramid scheme business proposal</dare>
    <dare id="d19">Hop like a frog and shout "PIKA-CHU" as loud and dramatically as you can</dare>
    <dare id="d20">Do the squidward ab crunches while yelling "Future!"</dare>
    <dare id="d21">Call someone a "bitch ass nigger" with the hard R</dare>
    <dare id="d22">Prank call someone by pretending to order pineapple pizza with anchovies</dare>
    <dare id="d23">Have someone spit in your mouth</dare>
    <dare id="d24">Have someone pick their nose and rub it on your cheeks</dare>
    <dare id="d25">Have someone pin you against the wall and ask "what? no dinner first?"</dare>
    <dare id="d26">Seduce someone that isn't your partner</dare>
    <dare id="d27">Yell out "I want daddy Trump to touch me inappropriately as loud as you can"</dare>
    <dare id="d28">Yell out the window "I want my money and I want it now! as loud as you can"</dare>
    <dare id="d29">Grind your crotch against the floor as gay as possible</dare>
    <dare id="d30">Drink a shot of water after they drip their tongue in it</dare>
    <dare id="d31">Kiss on the cheek of someone who isn't your partner</dare>
    <dare id="d32">Have someone choke you while looking aroused</dare>
    <dare id="d33">Rub someone's ass of the same sex and say "I know you want this D"</dare>
    <dare id="d34">Have someone princess carry you across the room</dare>
    <dare id="d35">Have someone dry doggystyle you while they spank you</dare>
    <dare id="d36">Give your best dying act</dare>
    <dare id="d37">Blindfold yourself and let someone feed you a "mystery snack"</dare>
    <dare id="d38">Let someone who isn't your partner look through your text messages</dare>
    <dare id="d39">Text a relative that you're coming out as gay</dare>
    <dare id="d40">Sniff the armpit of someone who isn't your partner</dare>
    <dare id="d41">Have someone who isn't your partner sit on your lap until your next turn</dare>
    <dare id="d42">Call someone to let them know you're pregnant/got someone pregnant and naming
      your kid after them</dare>
    <dare id="d43">Put on blindfold and have someone who isn't your partner touch you in any way</dare>
    <dare id="d44">Get into a dark closet with someone of the same sex for a minute and make moaning
      noises</dare>
    <dare id="d45">Have someone's feet that isn't your partner placed on your face</dare>
    <dare id="d46">Act out any of your favorite video game until someone guess it right</dare>
    <dare id="d47">Act out any of your favorite movie until someone guess it right</dare>
    <dare id="d48">Act out any of your favorite character until someone guess it right</dare>
    <dare id="d49">Act out someone you know personally until someone guess it right</dare>
    <dare id="d50">Sing a song that is in a language that you don't understand at all. Give it a
      good performance</dare>
    <dare id="d51">Give someone a very serious conversation in a language you don't understand</dare>
    <dare id="d52">Propose for marriage to someone of the same sex</dare>
    <dare id="d53">Dry hump someone's leg and say "Don't leave me daddy/mommy"</dare>
    <dare id="d54">Mock someone until your next turn</dare>
    <dare id="d55">Imitate someone until your next turn</dare>
    <dare id="d56">Skip around the room while singing "I'm a barbie girl"</dare>
    <dare id="d57">Give someone that isn't your partner a back massage until your next turn</dare>
    <dare id="d58">Give someone that isn't your partner a foot rub until your next turn</dare>
    <dare id="d59">Act out any of your favorite villian until someone guess it right</dare>
    <dare id="d60">Do a plank for at least 30 seconds</dare>
    <dare id="d61">Act like a fish out of water while maintaining eye contact with someone</dare>
    <dare id="d62">Perform 10 burpees</dare>
    <dare id="d63">Perform 10 squats</dare>
    <dare id="d64">Rap to your favorite hip hop music</dare>
    <dare id="d65">Sing a song from a musical with someone</dare>
    <dare id="d66">Perform 10 crunches</dare>
    <dare id="d67">Sing someone else's favorite song that you never heard before</dare>
    <dare id="d68">Run across the room in your underwear saying "I'm freeeee!"</dare>
    <dare id="d69">Maintain a constant eye contact with someone until your next turn </dare>
    <dare id="d70">Hug someone's arm and rest on their shoulders that isn't your partner until your
      next turn</dare>
    <dare id="d71">Show everyone the last porn video you watched</dare>
    <dare id="d72">Rollover like a dog then start panting like one</dare>
  </dares>
</truthdare>